[
    {
        "Question": "Which horror author penned the apocalyptic novel 'The Stand'? ",
        "Answer": "Stephen King"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which book about a band of rabbits became a bestseller in 1972? ",
        "Answer":  "Watership Down"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "The classic 1877 novel 'Black Beauty' is about what kind of animal? ",
        "Answer":  "Horse"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who was the first author to use a 'typemachine' or typewriter in writing a manuscript?",
        "Answer":  "Mark Twain"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "What 1988 book by Salman Rushdie is considered blasphemous by many Muslim countries?",
        "Answer":  "The Satanic Verses"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which mystery writer holds the Guinness World Record for the most translated works?",
        "Answer":  "Agatha Christie"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "What book holds the record for the fastest selling book in history? ",
        "Answer":  "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "'Call me Ishmael' is the first line from what classic novel?",
        "Answer":  "Moby Dick"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "What Charles Dickens novel begins with the sentence, 'It was the best of times, it was the worst of times'",
        "Answer":  "A Tale of Two Cities"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "What popular young adult book series sends 'tributes' to participate in a televised competition in which they fight to the death? ",
        "Answer":  "The Hunger Games"  
    },
    {
        "Question": "Jacob Black is a character in what Stephenie Meyer book series? ",
        "Answer": "Twilight"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What Nicholas Sparks book about a young socialite and her long-time crush was made into a movie starring Ryan Gosling and Rachel McAdams?",
        "Answer": "The Notebook"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In one of the most popular Dr. Seuss books, what won't Sam-I-Am eat? ",
        "Answer": "Green eggs and ham"
    }
]
